Contact

djit53@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jit-das-(LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Social Media
Digital Marketing
Consulting

Certifications

IAB Digital Marketing and Media Foundations Certification

Certified Professional Autodesk Revit Architecture 2013

Certified Professional AutoCAD Civil 3D 2013

Jit Das

Digital Marketing | PR and Media Outreach | Link Building | IEO | ICO | STO | Blockchain Enthusiast

Indore

Summary

Hi! Thanks for crossing by my profile.

Myself Satyajit, I'm Tech-Savvy and Experienced Public Relations Consultant with a demonstrated history of working in the Public Relations and Communications industry. Skilled in media relations, content creation, PR planning & execution. Strong media and communication professional with a Post Graduate Diploma in Media Management focused in Public Relations and Digital Marketing.

Experience

Freelancer

Public Relations Specialist November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Indore, Madhya Pradesh, India

Public Relations professionals help a business or individual cultivate a positive reputation with the public through various unpaid or earned communications, including traditional media, social media, and in-person engagements. They also help clients defend their reputation during a crisis that threatens their credibility. A PR professional works with an organization, company, government, or individual to cultivate a story that portrays that client's reputation, idea, product, position, or accomplishment in a positive light. So, in a sense, you can think of PR professionals as storytellers. Unlike advertisers, who tell stories through paid methods, PR professionals tell their stories through unpaid or earned media.

Freelancer

Digital Marketing Consultant July 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Indore, Madhya Pradesh, India

Digital marketing encompasses all marketing efforts that use an electronic device or the internet. Businesses leverage digital channels such as search engines, social media, email, and other websites to connect with current and prospective customers. A seasoned inbound marketer might say inbound

marketing and digital marketing are virtually the same thing, but there are some minor differences. And conversations with marketers and business owners in the U.S., U.K., Asia, Australia, and New Zealand, I've learned a lot about how those small differences are being observed across the world.

Larsen & Toubro Graduate Management Trainee June 2017 - May 2018 (1 year) Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Graduate Engineer Trainee is a designation when you first enter into a company just after completing your graduation. During this period you would be learning about the company, its various departments and how they work. Usually, you are not given any responsibility in terms of work and supposed to follow your experienced peers and get familiar with your responsibilities when you take charge. In simple words, it's watch and learn period.

Education

Indian Business School of Advanced Management Studies (IBSAMS)

Master's degree, Communication and Media Studies · (2018 - 2020)

Jadavpur University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Civil Engineering · (2013 - 2017)